I'm going to stress you to tell you the third board meeting for Monday, November 4th, 2024.
And we're going to have the implication by retired pastor, first Chris McCurkey, which is really
always. He gave the permission to take 30 seconds, is that all right, to say something.
The other night, new neighborhood, 200 plus trick or treaters.
But later I thought, every 98% of the kids said thank you.
And one of the pleasures to meet with us to see a family together and give us a, you're doing a good job.
But I feel that about our communities. Let's break.
Father, I thank you for their dads and moms that took the kids out and we're with them and who've taught them.
Bless them, Lord. Help them in moments when they get discouraged and help our whole community Lord.
Maybe one thing you're going to run for.
They're just nervous about the future.
Thank you for the leaders we have to help us get through any tough times.
And Lord, I thank you especially for the people working here in this building and out from this building.
Bless them. Give them energy. Help them when they're tired of doing it.
And Lord, our group here tonight, continue to take care of each of them.
Give him and her wisdom.
And Lord, we ask you to just guide each of us as we live in this community.
Jesus name up for a.
Amen.
I play with you.
To the back of the United States as a mayor.
And to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God in the business.
We'll deliver to you as this is for all.
Awesome.
Four.
But again, but let's get the personal parents.
Five.
Much to approve.
Second.
A step.
Five.
Gidel Stratten Edmunds upon reclaimed for a little civil litigation in the amount of $4,386.46.
So this is what this work is relating to the regulation saying this is approved.
or 79,200,000, 300,000. Most of you approve.
He's the principal.
Bones, I've Parker.
Nine, Tetrotec client for civil litigation in the amount of $8,600.
So again, this is in regards to the relicence and addition to the other piece of land.
This is primarily...
Most of you approve.
I can accept.
I do.
Hi.
Dan, contract.
Amendment number one for C-23-53.
With clean uniform company, for uniform services, contingent upon submission of all required contract documents.
Last year, we started...
We set up a contract with clean uniform,
and they do our plight mats,
and clothing, and different things for the city and M-S-U-A.
We made the contract last year.
They will only do it every 12 months.
We want to get the amendment and want to prove to take it out another 12 months.
They kept all the same pricing.
I have prices if you guys need to see anything.
And we recommend accepting amendment one with clean uniform.
Motion to approve.
So full.
Aye.
Orn's aye.
E-Step.
Aye.
11.
Another new business of any of which is written as opposed to this agenda.
12 staff reports.
13 trustee community announcements.
14.
This meeting will be continuing to the council chambers,
to reach me in the staff room,
for the purpose of the executive session at the completion of the regular meeting of the M-I-P-F-A.